

Filbert

Front End Developer - IT Support (+62) 87777245031

Filbert10.work@gmail.com



Jakarta, Indonesia

I have approximately six months of experience in IT support, where I have demonstrated my skills in installing and maintaining software and hardware systems, performing remote troubleshooting, and updating company TV ads. I have also gained experience in making MySQL queries to add and remove product stock. I have also continued the company's program project with ReactJS and React Native for approximately six months, where I have gained experience in testing applications and fixing bugs in program code.

Hi, I am Filbert, a graduate of a Bachelor of Science program in Information Technology. I am a reliable and hardworking team player with a strong desire to learn new things.





Work Experience

Business Owner • Saltpartners Group

June 2023 - September 2023



- Establish and maintain professional relationships and communication with others.
- Expand the team and build a strong team with a positive and effective leader.
- Hold a charity event every month as a way to express gratitude for the progress we have made and the development of the team.

Front End Developer • PT. Uruz Solusi Teknologi



November 2022 - April 2023

- Develop mobile applications using ReactNative and websites using ReactJS.
- Communicate with leaders and UI/UX teams about changes to the UI.
- Build communication between divisions with leaders.
- Fix software bugs that are found.

Administrator • PT. Vysco Indo Pratama



May 2022 - October 2022

- Prepare daily reports on fuel consumption and plantation work results.
- Prepare monthly reports on total fuel consumption, plantation work blocks, and the area of plantation work blocks.
- Prepare invoices for vehicle and goods shipments.
- Build communication between plantation blocks divisions and employees.
- Perform cross-checks between accounting records and invoices. Create report and analyzed monthly usage petrol and summary works.

IT Support Intern • Orang Tua Group



- Troubleshoots application software, database issues and web application system on a timely basis.
- Assist company in troubleshooting problems, diagnose issues with software installation (Microsoft Office, etc.) and application (Oracle, etc.), identify sources of the problem and offer solutions.
- Involved in the creation of new software and work closely with software engineers and development teams to identify and resolve potential issues in the development stage.
- Analyze all aspects of the software and make suggestions throughout the development phase to help avoid issues in the final product.
- Determine, review criticality and prioritize resolution of issues.
- Resolve cases and provide updates to company
- Instalation and troubleshooting IT Devices (PC / AIO, Printer, Projector, etc) and Network (Proxy, DNS, etc) and User account Setting.

UI/UX Intern • Orang Tua Group

OO BEYOND³¹

August 2021 - August 2021

- Identifying User Experience problems from the products and system to understand how to create a better user experience based on user's needs.
- Create reliable mockups to visualize the solution that is relevant to the user's problems and needs.
- Create prototypes that clearly illustrate how the product functions and interacts with users.
- Create design assets such as UI Components, Icons and Illustrations. Identifying User Experience problems from the products and system to understand how to create a better user experience based on user's needs. Create reliable mockups to visualize the solution that is relevant to the user's problems and needs. Create prototypes that clearly illustrate how the product functions and interacts with users. Create design assets such as UI Components, Icons and Illustrations.

Fullstack Developer Intern • Orang Tua Group



July 2021 - July 2021

- Learn C# and mySQL for advancing on creating an software for corporation.
- Gather and analyze user requirements, design and develop as well configure system
- Design and develop cross-platform mobile application including android and mobile web.

Education

2018 - 2022

Tarumanagara University

Bachelor of Information Technology

Skills Troubleshooting **Programming Language** Language Computer Java Chinese Network C++ English Printers React JS Indonesia Mobile Phones React Native HTML/CSS